{
    "subject": "resource/Carly_Rose_Sonenclar",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Carly Rose Sonenclar (born April 20, 1999) is an American singer and teen actress. In December 2012, she became the runner-up on the second season of the American version of the The X Factor.On May 29, 2014, Sonenclar was labeled as one of the most 'influential' X Factor USA contestants of all-time by FoxWeekly, for her audition performance of 'Feeling Good'.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Carly Rose Sonenclar is: Carly Rose Sonenclar (born April 20, 1999) is an American singer and teen actress. In December 2012, she became the runner-up on the second season of the American version of the The X Factor. On May 29, 2014, Sonenclar was labeled as one of the most 'influential' X Factor USA contestants of all-time by FoxWeekly, for her audition performance of 'Feeling Good'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9407719969749451,
            "question": "Which magazine labeled Carly Rose Sonenclar as one of the most 'influential' X Factor USA contestants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8888460397720337,
            "question": "In what year did Carly Rose Sonenclar become the runner-up on The X Factor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8266427516937256,
            "question": "Is Carly Rose Sonenclar American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.820902943611145,
            "question": "When was Carly Rose Sonenclar born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8196830153465271,
            "question": "What song did Carly Rose Sonenclar perform for her audition on The X Factor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8159408569335938,
            "question": "What year was Carly Rose Sonenclar recognized by FoxWeekly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8058090209960938,
            "question": "What season of The X Factor did Carly Rose Sonenclar compete on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6756624579429626,
            "question": "What is Carly Rose Sonenclar's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.641879141330719,
            "question": "What television show did Carly Rose Sonenclar appear on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6078211665153503,
            "question": "Besides singing, what other profession does Carly Rose Sonenclar have?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Carly Rose Sonenclar is: Carly Rose Sonenclar (born April 20, 1999) is an American singer and teen actress. In December 2012, she became the runner-up on the second season of the American version of the The X Factor. On May 29, 2014, Sonenclar was labeled as one of the most 'influential' X Factor USA contestants of all-time by FoxWeekly, for her audition performance of 'Feeling Good'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7216_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What television show did Carly Rose Sonenclar appear on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7216_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Carly Rose Sonenclar's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7216_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What season of The X Factor did Carly Rose Sonenclar compete on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7216_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7216_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7216_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7216_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7216_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7216_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7216_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7216_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7216_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7216_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7216_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that the provided text does indeed support the triple. \n\nHere is the structured JSON format containing the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context about Carly Rose Sonenclar includes details that match the query. Specifically, it mentions that she was born on April 20, 1999, is an American singer and actress, and was a runner-up in the second season of The X Factor USA in December 2012. Additionally, her performance of \"Feeling Good\" was recognized as influential by FoxWeekly on May 29, 2014. Therefore, the information supports the given query statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}